Hey, let's do it!
Can I go to
Jesus' room?
Of course, Privi, you
can go to Jesus'
room if you're a
man.
But it's not!
He wants to go
to the river, and
he's going to the
river.
To make him know
how he's going to
be.
Because I know.
I'm going to run.
It's time.
I'm going to run,
and I'm going to
the river.
So it's a little
bit difficult for me
to...
I'm going to get
a little bit deeper
in the river.
What are you going
to do?
Well, that's not a
problem.
The end is to
give you the chance
to let your soul
see how he's going
to be.
And it's not going
to be a religion.
It's going to be
a relationship with you.
What's a relationship?
What do we do?
We talk to each
other.
We pay, we make
time for each other.
And that's what he
also says about you.
And how do you
feel about it?
Why do I have
to change things?
Life style.
No.
I think so.
Change the lifestyle.
It's going to come.
The important thing is
now that you think
of the way you
think.
Change.
Not to the world,
in the sense of
life style etc.
But to the point
I get the right
one.
And the rest is
full.
Is it difficult or
easy?
Or how can I
see it?
Jesus is not easy.
It's not always nice.
But the important thing
is that you have
every relationship you have.
And when you look
at it, it's worth
it.
I think it's worth
I'm going to open
it.
Yes.
Then I have one
question.
That's it.
I'll give you a
box of red shoes.
hand.
Amen.